== Official || kisskh.asia - kissasia.co ||for Support ==
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds…)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
(Episode 4)
(Gipyeong Rest Stop)
(2026 Durumi Electronics Sales Team Workshop)
Oh, dear.
Manager Lee. I'll have a latte.
- Yes. I need to use the restroom.
- Gosh, it hurts.
Okay, go ahead.
Team Leader Han.
Well, I wonder if you remember.
We made a drinking bet yesterday.
The first one to pass out had to buy snacks at the rest stop.
- Team Leader Bong.
- Yes?
Team Leader Bong.
Here you go.
Gosh, thank you, Team Leader Han.
I'll try not to go too wild with this.
No, no. Go all out. Go big. Real big.
All right. I'll really go for it.
Guys! Let's eat.
What's going on?
Why does that guy scare me?
What?
Did I dream yesterday?
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
Why am I so sore and stiff?
Oh, my neck.
- Manager Yu.
- Yes?
Here, drink this. It'll help.
A hangover cure?
I don't have a hangover. You drink it.
- I see. You don't have a hangover.
- No.
You were so cool yesterday, Manager Yu.
Why? Did something happen yesterday?
It was nothing.
Oh, right. You did well.
It was your first time in the field, so it must've been chaotic, right?
You did a good job.
Thank you.
Manager Yu. There's one thing I'm curious about.
What is it?
Why did you deal with those bastards like that yesterday?
Differently from the other Meetings?
Didn't you hear? It was a preliminary Meeting.
It hurts so much.
It hurts so bad...
My back.
Darn it.
Sir.
They turned themselves in?
Right at dawn, a call came into the station.
This old man, saying he wanted to confess.
He confessed to everything without even being asked.
He buried all seven of the missing people after removing their organs.
He was even kind enough to give us the location.
He said he did it in that warehouse over there.
The forensics team is collecting DNA samples now.
But why is everyone in this condition?
They claim they got into a fight amongst themselves.
To the point they ended up like this?
They won't say what they fought over, so we don't know. But that's their story.
What about recent guests?
They haven't been in business for the past month,
so there were no guests. Naturally, there's no guest list either.
- Have you checked the CCTV?
- About that...
The strange thing is...
There's nothing. Not a single thing.
What do you mean? Was it erased?
Well, according to them, it was turned off.
So we don't know if it was erased,
or if it never recorded anything to begin with.
In my 15 years as a detective,
this is the first time I've had a case handed to me on a platter...
We have evidence from the scene and even a confession.
So even without the CCTV footage...
But...
(Checkpoint, Reduce Speed)
Get out of the car.
I said, get out.
I told you I'm in a hurry. I have to go now.
I'm responding to an emergency call.
I understand. Now show me your ID.
Gosh, you're so diligent. Please, just let me go.
My gosh. Where do you think you're going?
Someone is dying right now.
I have to perform CPR, you get it? I'm leaving now.
I get it. Now show me your ID.
This guy... Get him. Get him.
- Hey, get him. Get him.
- Darn it...
Beom, what's wrong?
An ambulance was heading to the bed and breakfast,
so we stopped it for inspection,
and the man inside suddenly tried to run, so we got him.
- I see.
- He's wearing a doctor's coat.
I think he's the organ harvesting specialist.
- A specialist?
- Hurry, get your ID out. Now.
Get him. Get him!
- Hurry up. Get it out.
- Okay, okay.
What's his name?
Jo Dong Min?
It's not Jo Dong Min.
It's Jo Dong Man. It's Man.
He says it's Jo Dong Man? Did you check his ID?
Mr. Jo is pretty good at what he does.
Our clients are scheduled to arrive one every hour,
so if you wait on the road to the bed and breakfast,
you can just pick them off one by one.
- Got it.
- My hands are falling asleep.
He said a client is coming every hour, so maintain the checkpoint.
- Who are you flies buzzing around me?
- Flies?
Die, you wench!
On your knees, you bastard.
Hey, get up. On your knees.
Get on your knees, you bastards. Kneel.
If you hand them over to the police, isn't it just a waste of time?
They won't be punished properly anyway.
And how would you know that?
Whether they'll be properly punished or not.
The police, the law, the courts...
Do you just blindly distrust and oppose them?
No. It's not necessarily like that.
A preliminary meeting means we entrust it to the law first.
It means we respect its role and responsibilities.
Of course, there can be limitations.
Sometimes a verdict functions as the minimum punishment,
and sometimes, impure things that shouldn't interfere
get in the way of rightful punishment by law.
But it's not right to just ignore and cast it aside.
We're not trying to create a lawless world, are we?
They do their job, and we do ours. That's how I see it.
We just sometimes do the things they can't.
Manager Yu.
But then again, who knows?
Maybe the day will come when today's
preliminary meeting becomes an official one.
If they forget us.
If they forget that somewhere out there, there are beings scarier than the law.
A gang of inhuman organ traffickers
who kidnapped hikers to harvest organs and bury their bodies
has been arrested by the police.
The victims they kidnapped and murdered
have all been previously reported as part of
the Mount Taegong serial disappearance case,
and have now been identified as the missing hikers.
(Do Not Enter)
Police announced today
that they have recovered the bodies of all the victims
who were secretly buried in mountains across the country.
As for the hospitals that purchased organs from the traffickers,
and performed illegal surgeries,
they have been raided and all personnel arrested.
Police have obtained a list of the individuals
who received the illegal transplants,
and are expanding the investigation to the entire medical community.
In addition to a full-scale crackdown on the illegal organ black market,
they believe there are other medical institutions
that have committed similar crimes,
and plan to track them down and punish them severely.
Let's hope they remember.
That for those who take their crimes lightly and scoff at the law,
when they feel most safe and at ease,
the harshest punishment of all will come for them.
Oh, I see. So you're rooting for Kingfisher, then?
Yes, sir, I've noted your expert opinion. But since we're the police,
we have a duty we have to uphold.
(Beom Sung Hoon)
Seriously, they said it was a tip,
but they just called to tell us not to catch Kingfisher.
Give me a break.
Tell me about it.
Every time a major violent crime case breaks,
they'd think Kingfisher was the most precious person in the world.
Gosh. How are we supposed to get any work done with all this commotion?
It'll be 1 or 2 months at most.
They're bound to strike somewhere else soon, right?
- Make sure the chief has his meals.
- Okay.
We're heading out for the stakeout in Inseong-dong.
- Good work.
- We're heading out.
(Violent Crimes Unit 1)
Take care out there.
Wow, look at the time.
Should I order dinner?
The victims.
Sir?
When you hit a wall with the perpetrators, you go after the victims.
So far, Kingfisher's pattern has been from 7 days to 60 days max.
Just as Detective Jang said, they'll strike again somewhere soon.
Instead of focusing on a past crime, what if we go after a future one?
A future crime?
Kingfisher's next target.
The next target? Who?
- No, I'm not going.
- Why not?
Your daycare is going to the kids' cafe today.
- It'll be so much fun.
- But Mommy's not coming.
Yul, Mommy told you she can't because she has to go to work, right?
That's right, Yul. Mommy can't go because she has to work today.
Instead, Daddy will buy you new Baby Shark stickers tonight.
- How about that?
- No, I don't want them.
This isn't working. Honey, you go on ahead.
You said you have an out-of-town story and have to leave early. Go.
It's still fine.
- We'll get up in a minute. Right, Yul?
- No, I'm not getting up.
Kwon Yul, if you don't get up by the time I count to five,
I'm going to forcibly get you up and drag you out of here.
- Is that what you want?
- No, don't.
I'm counting.
One.
Two...
So scary. I think Yul needs to get up now.
You know Mommy doesn't play around when she's mad, right?
Three.
Here I come. Four.
Mommy doesn't play around.
"Doesn't play around."
My daughter is so smart.
Give it here.
Right?
Your mom shows no mercy, right?
Your mom has always been that merciless.
I was so scared when I first met your mom.
So scary. Let's go, let's go. So scary.
(Child On Board)
Yul, what did Mommy tell you to do at the kids' cafe today?
Listen to your teacher, don't fight with your friends,
and be careful not to get hurt. Right?
You have to do that. Got it?
It's Seo Jun. Mommy, it's Seo Jun.
- I don't want to.
- No. Sweetie.
- I'm not going.
- Mommy's running late. Let's go.
My car went in for repairs yesterday,
and I couldn't get a taxi for the life of me.
Then he threw a tantrum today, saying he didn't want to go to daycare.
That must have been tough.
They say "terrible fours," and that's my son exactly these days.
It's a war every morning.
And my commute is already a battle since my office is so far.
My mommy goes to work too.
That's right, Yul.
You work too?
I was on maternity leave, and I just went back to work recently.
This is just the beginning for me.
I didn't know.
My mommy won't come to the kids' cafe.
Yul, right?
If you just went back, it must be really tough for you.
Going back to the office after only looking after your kid
at home every day,
your feelings must be all over the place these days, right?
When you're home, you miss working,
but when you work,
you can't stop worrying about the child you left behind.
Is it like that for you too?
It was even worse for me.
I went back to work right after his first birthday.
That's why I feel especially guilty on days like today.
- The other moms all volunteer for this.
- I hate you, Mommy.
Park Seo Jun.
You shouldn't say such mean things to your mother.
Ridiculous, right?
I hate you, Mommy.
Yul, do you hate Mommy too?
I'm sorry.
Oh, dear.
- Go on in.
- Go on in. We'll see you later.
- Bye.
- Oh my.
What's with the two of them all of a sudden?
Misery loves company. Helping each other out.
- Hello.
Hello, ma'am.
Oh my, Seo Jun and Yul came together today.
You little brat.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's all right.
Ma'am, please take good care of him again today.
Yul's mom, thank you so much for today.
I'll treat you to coffee.
- It's fine.
- I have to go.
Yes, you should get going. Bye.
Yul, you have to say goodbye to Mommy too. Come on, sweetie.
Get along with your friends today...
You're leaving without saying goodbye?
Don't worry too much, ma'am.
Please take good care of her.
(Joa Daycare Center)
Oh dear, Yul seems especially down today.
It's her way of protesting against her mom.
Her mom must be heartbroken. Oh, no.
What do you mean, "Oh, no?"
Both the mother and the child have to get over it.
(Reform The Mind, Correct The Behavior)
1503, Pyo Gyu Cheol, you're released.
Don't you have any belongings?
I don't need anything.
Gosh, that punk. Acting all tough now that he's out.
(Durumi Electronics)
(Joa Daycare Center)
Pyo Gyu Cheol. As per the court order, from this moment,
I will be fitting you with an electronic ankle monitor.
Okay.
Just get this over with quickly.
Hey. Be gentle.
Go now. Run, run!
- Goodness.
- Look at us go.
Say cheese.
Let's go.
Slowly. That's a big one, Hae Yi.
That's it. Oh, so pretty. Yul.
Yul.
Yul, give me a peace sign. Are you not in the mood for a picture?
- Mom.
- Yul, do want to do it with Mommy?
Here, look.
The mouse. Okay, aim right for the mouse's head.
Yul, look.
It's going up.
First place.
Yul, you did great.
Be careful, be careful.
Look here. Say cheese.
Ye Geon, be careful. Careful.
Kids will be kids.
I thought you couldn't make it. What brings you here?
It wasn't anything particularly urgent,
so I just asked for permission at work and took a half-day off.
Good for you. You left after seeing her so down.
How could you possibly focus on work?
If only kids understood how we mothers feel,
- wouldn't that be great?
- Kids are all like that at this age.
It's an age where they develop a sense of self,
but they're still self-centered.
Understanding other people's perspectives
is only possible from age six.
That's right.
It's important to teach kids the rules of daily life at this age,
but it's not easy.
- I find that incredibly difficult.
- Me too.
I mean, sometimes they say to be firm, and other times to be lenient.
They say to balance being strict and gentle,
so the kids don't get confused.
I mean, that's easier said than done. Is that even possible?
It's difficult and tough.
But...
They say this is the most precious time for a mother and child.
The memories that form the bond between a mother and child
- are created around this time.
- Start.
Oh, my sweet child.
How pretty.
Ye Geon, be careful.
Be careful.
What is this?
Why is that bastard getting out?
- What? Who's getting out?
- Pyo Gyu Cheol.
- Look at this.
- I'm here
at the main gate of Jungryeong Prison, where tensions are running high.
Fierce protests from many citizens have been ongoing
since early this morning.
Pyo Gyu Cheol, known as the nation's worst child sex offender,
is being released today after serving a 16-year sentence.
The inclusion of an eight-year-old child among his victims
has caused great shock and public outrage.
Pyo Gyu Cheol's Law.
The laws punishing sex crimes against children
were significantly strengthened in 2010,
but because Pyo Gyu Cheol's crime was subject to the law prior to 2009,
he was released after serving a relatively short sentence of only 16 years.
Enraged by this, citizens
have demanded the retroactive application of the strengthened law.
How could anyone do that to an eight-year-old child?
I mean, the mom forums are already going crazy about this,
and that guy is really getting out? Why?
Why else? They're letting him out because he served his time.
Well, then, to make sure he'd never get out,
they should have given him a harsher sentence in the first place.
- Exactly. Isn't this totally insane?
- Seriously. If I had my way right now,
I'd call Kingfisher this very second.
But I can't because I don't have the number.
- But I'm so angry.
- What do we do now?
How are we supposed to live when the world is so terrifying?
I'm so furious right now.
The law really needs to change. It does.
What are we going to do?
I mean, how can we let our kids play outside
with things like this happening?
I can't.
As a father raising a daughter,
I felt I had to do something, so I came out here.
I mean, if a monster like that is out on the streets,
how can anyone feel safe letting their kids outside?
Why should we be the ones living in fear?
Okay, thank you for the interview.
- He's coming out.
He's coming out.
Go to hell, you piece of scum. Give him the death penalty.
Just die.
(Building A Better Future Through Advanced Corrections)
That bastard.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
I've organized the past victims by crime type as you asked.
As expected, murder is the most common one.
I figured as much.
But this is strange.
Why does Kingfisher just leave those bastards alone?
Those kinds of bastards? What do you mean?
The ones who go after kids. Like child sex offenders.
I mean, there isn't a single one among his victims.
Honestly, given the severity of the crime, aren't they the absolute worst?
They have a high reoffending rate too.
Beom.
I want you to track
the child sex offenders released in the last 15 years.
Track them?
- For what?
- To see if they're still alive and well.
(Violent Crimes Unit 2)
I've narrowed down the child sex offenders released
in the last 15 years to just the worst ones,
and it comes out to about eight people.
And?
Now, here are three facts that will blow your mind.
One, all eight of them are dead.
- What?
- Two, how did they die?
From all sorts of accidents. Car crashes, drowning, falls,
electrocution, things like that.
- Accidents?
- Three, this is the most shocking part.
All on the very day they were released from prison,
they died.
This is all very suspicious, don't you think? Right?
Sounds unbelievable, right?
When is Pyo Gyu Cheol getting released?
Pyo Gyu Cheol.
Do you really think Pyo Gyu Cheol is Kingfisher's next target?
But there's no proof linking
the dead child sex offenders to Kingfisher.
It is not like they were shot to death.
This is too much of a coincidence. So I'm willing to grasp at straws.
I guess we'll find out after watching him for a day.
Stay on him.
Yes, sir.
Pyo Gyu Cheol.
Did you see that?
Did you?
All those people are protesting your release.
They're parents with children.
Bullshit.
Did I mess with their kids?
They should be watching their own brats. Why are they butting in?
(Samneung Rest Area)
Hey, we have time. Let's stop at the rest area.
It's been a while since I've gotten fresh air,
and now I have to take a shit. You know?
I said I have to take a shit.
Hey, I'm talking to you. Shit.
There you go. You have to make eye contact. Shit.
Nice.
Looks like he's pulling into the rest area.
- Go.
- Yes, sir.
Are you even human? You're worse than an animal.
How could anyone do that to those little angels? Seriously.
This bastard...
If I were not a reporter,
I'd smack you so hard.
Kwon.
What are you doing here by yourself?
This is a great picture.
Do you want to see it?
I got all the interviews with the protestors.
Good work. What did they say?
They were all asking how they're supposed to raise kids in a world like this.
They all had a lot to say.
They said that at the minimum, child sex offenders
should get sentences of hundreds of years, like they do abroad.
I guess they were speaking your mind?
That's because all parents feel the same way.
Let's go. We need to check out...
Pyo Gyu Cheol's residence and the probation office.
Okay.
- Want some of this?
- Let's blow some bubbles.
Yul, look over here at Mommy.
Seo Jun and Yul, look over here. Smile.
Seo Jun, you look here too.
Wow, you blew that so well.
- Everyone, look here.
- She's taking a picture.
- I got some on me too.
- What are you going to eat?
Is it good?
(Seo Jun's Mother)
Seo Jun's mother.
Seo Jun is having a great time, so do not worry.
Yul's mom, Are you looking after my Seo Jun too?
Thank you so much.
Did you go to the kids' cafe? But I thought you said you couldn't go.
I guess it takes a mom to know another.
We should get a meal together with the kids sometime.
Yul, here. Eat this while you play.
No.
(Samneung Rest Stop, Men's Restroom, Second Stall, Knock)
(The toilet clogs. Please throw wet wipes in the trach. If it gets clogged...)
This is such a filthy job. I can't take this anymore. Darn it.
I mean, why do we have to take a bastard like him by car,
and politely escort him all the way home?
Especially when we're already so short-staffed.
I don't even know what I'm doing anymore.
Am I supposed to be watching this bastard or protecting him? Darn it.
Goodness.
What's he doing, making the crap from scratch?
Why isn't he coming out?
What's this?
Darn it, what's going on?
What is it?
- Excuse me, sorry.
- What's happening? What is it?
Detective Lee, over here.
It says the bastard is outside.
Hey, you think that bastard escaped through the window?
Hurry, hurry.
(Samneung)
Sir, over there.
(Men's Restroom)
Detective Lee, you drive.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Wait a minute.
- Yes?
- Where's Pyo Gyu Cheol?
Look, he can't have gone far, so let's hurry and go after him.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Reporter Koo, get in. Hurry.
- Sir, where are we going?
- I don't know, but
it looks like something's happened to Pyo Gyu Cheol. Let's just go.
(Not Today)
Filthy bastard. Darn it.
(Men's Restroom)
Sir, welcome.
You did well.
Did Park Hui Dong send you?
Of course.
He's at Samjin Port now.
Name, Park Hui Dong.
A fellow inmate who shared a cell with Pyo Gyu Cheol.
Park Hui Dong served three years for producing,
and distributing digital pornography, and was released three months ago.
According to our in tel, after Pyo Gyu Cheol is released,
he'll team up with Park Hui Dong and illegally leave the country,
where we expect them to set up a base and start producing child pornography.
Shit. Wow, that's insane.
Let's start with the scenario.
The meeting date is on the day of his release, as expected.
But I think we should move up the timeline.
Before he goes back to his old neighborhood.
During his transfer?
Well, that could get messy.
His last victim still lives in that neighborhood.
Samneung Rest Stop is 30 minutes from Jungryeong Prison.
We'll grab him there.
Then, two hours from there is Mount Jeongan.
There's a small birch forest there.
A place Pyo Gyu Cheol would absolutely hate.
You have a pollen allergy.
That's why I don't usually go to the mountains.
In the spring, you should watch out for birch trees,
and in the fall, you'll need to be careful of ragweed.
I'll prepare the allergy medication.
So he can have a little taste of hell.
Okay, okay.
Let's keep it simple.
A guy just released from prison cuts off his electronic ankle monitor,
and flees into the mountains.
On a spring day of all days, he just happens to pass by a birch forest,
when he has a seizure from his chronic pollen allergy,
and falls to his death from a cliff.
Anyway, you've got some darn good friends.
You know, in life,
it's hard to meet people you click with, right?
Well, let me make one phone call.
To whom?
Oh, that friend of yours?
You're so suspicious.
Here. Go ahead.
(President Park)
(President Park, 010-645-6490)
(Call Blocked)
The number you have dialed is not available.
You will be redirected to voicemail...
(Call Blocked)
The number you have dialed is not available.
Honestly. You've got a lot of time on your hands.
Hey, if you don't trust me, then don't get in.
Then I'm not going either.
Goodness.
I mean, look, President Park paid me a hefty sum,
and begged and pleaded that you had to leave today,
so I even canceled my meeting to come here for this.
And I brought an expert to take off that ankle monitor for you.
This ankle monitor?
Hey, not just anyone can take that off. It's a huge pain in the ass.
All right, fine. Then you can just stand around here dawdling,
and get caught by the cops for all I care. That's none of my business, you hear?
Another thing.
When the party involved refuses...
You know the fee is absolutely non-refundable, right?
So damn suspicious. Goodness.
Hey, what are you doing? Get in, get in. Let's go home.
We came here for nothing.
Well, anyway, you really picked a great day.
This is the perfect weather for skipping town.
Before we skip town, let's stop by my old neighborhood.
What? If you go to your house now, there'll be people
swarming all over the place.
And if you go, you'll see things you shouldn't, right?
Who said anything about going home?
Oh, then where to?
It's just that before I go on this long journey,
I should at least see her face once.
I'm curious to see how she's grown...
Well, she was about 8 then, so if I add about 10-something years...
Wow, she must be all grown up now.
Do you really have to go that far?
Nice work, Manager Tae.
Oh, you look comfortable...
Let's switch back.
Gosh, I'm just not suited for big cars.
There's something I've been wondering.
Why do you use such complicated methods, like faking an accident?
A single shot from Kingfisher would make it so much easier.
We could do that,
but there are too many variables for one person to handle.
Especially since we're in charge of White.
White... Why?
Cleanly, painlessly, with a single shot.
That's Senior Bo Na's way.
I already knew that.
One shot, one kill. Kingfisher's signature.
Do you know why that is?
Because...
Because she's good.
It looks like the driver was drowsy.
(Rest Area For Drowsy Drivers)
We need to hurry.
This is the truck.
(Name: Pyo Gyu Cheol. 1973.11.04, Sex: M, Child Sexual Violence)
Beom, check on top.
Yes, sir.
Police.
Stay where you are. We need your cooperation.
Darn it.
Gosh, that scared me.
I thought it was a dismembered corpse.
Why go to all this trouble?
They could've just dumped it somewhere.
First, let's request cooperation
from the highway patrol and nearby precincts,
and set up checkpoints on the surrounding access roads.
We also need to secure the rest stop's CCTV footage quickly,
so let's move. We don't have time.
What's this?
Kwon Tae Sung. What are you doing here?
- Reporter Koo, hurry.
- Hey, hold on. Wait.
- Don't let them touch anything.
- Yes, sir.
- Please put the camera away. Put it away.
- Hey, wait. Hold on.
I'm sorry, can I just take one picture?
- I said no.
- Hey.
- Come on, why are you being like this?
- Were you tailing me? From where?
Tailing you? I happened to see you at the rest stop.
I was on my way back from covering Pyo Gyu Cheol's release.
You lost Pyo Gyu Cheol, didn't you?
Is this related to Kingfisher?
What?
Don't give me that. You're at the scene where you lost Pyo Gyu Cheol,
and the detective in charge of the Kingfisher case is here,
even though it's not your jurisdiction. A detective from Seoul, at that.
Why is this guy's intuition so good?
What is this?
Is it.
I'm just speculating at this point.
I came here thinking he might be the next target, but we've hit a dead end.
First, we need to find Pyo Gyu Cheol.
Whether he's alive or dead.
You're saying he could be dead?
Don't jump to conclusions. He could've just fled.
I'm busy, so get going.
Seriously, please don't.
- I'll just take one picture.
- Reporter Kwon Tae Sung.
I'm refusing to comment from now on.
Now, hurry up.
Don't take pictures.
- Get this out of here.
- Yes, sir.
The police are on the move.
There's a checkpoint at the tollgate 20km ahead.
- You should get off now.
- Okay.
- Let's take a detour.
Mommy first?
Delicious.
- Is it good, sweetie?
- Yes. It's so, so good.
- Is it yummy?
- Yes.
My Yul is in a great mood today.
Were you happy that Mommy came?
Yes. I was so, so happy.
Then maybe Mommy shouldn't go to work and stay by Yul's side every day. Right?
No, Mommy, go to work.
What? You want me to work? Why?
It's necessary work.
What?
Dad said he's not done with his work at the office yet.
- Want me to sing you a song?
- What kind of work?
Your dad...
Well, a very, very important job.
Your dad is a wonderful person who does great things for people.
What about you?
What?
What kind of work do you do?
I do... Well...
Necessary work.
Necessary work?
Yes.
Work the world needs.
Oh, you're such a smart girl.
(Pilhyeon 2-ri, Pilhyeon 1-ri)
(Baby On Board)
We shouldn't have come.
What's going on, sir?
Go, go. Quickly.
What?
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine.
That Pyo Gyu Cheol...
We're going to have to hold off because of the witness.
Get Pyo Gyu Cheol now.
- Get him.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, the bleeding won't stop. Your wound.
- Darn it.
- What do we do?
I said stop the car. Stop.
Oh, Dong Hoon, no. Dong Hoon!
- Dong Hoon. Dong Hoon.
- I'm Pyo Gyu Cheol, you bastards.
Who the hell sent you to kill me?
Hey, they're all still alive and well.
So why are you making such a big deal? You worthless scum.
- Mom...
- Who the hell is this kid?
Mom.
Dong Hoon.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Are you okay to drive?
Yes, I'm still okay.
Did you find Pyo Gyu Cheol?
Those bastards. Darn it.
This bastard hasn't been answering his phone.
Answer the phone, darn it.
What's this now?
That moron.
He didn't get far.
Can you confirm the GPS location?
Yes, I can.
It looks like he's heading toward Incheon.
I think he's trying to get on a boat.
- What's this?
- What now? Come on, what is it?
Gosh, that bastard. Darn it.
Mom, I want some gummies. Gummies.
What? Yul, sweetie, if you eat too much of that,
the doctor said sugar bugs will grow in your mouth.
Then we'll have to go to the dentist again.
Would you be okay with that?
- I don't want to.
- You don't, right?
Then how about we have some grilled fish today?
- How about some mackerel? You love that.
- I love mackerel.
- Yul, this mackerel...
- This is breaking news.
After a 16-year prison sentence,
child sex offender Pyo Gyu Cheol, who was released today,
has cut off his electronic ankle monitor and escaped while being transported.
The police have issued an emergency alert,
and they are focusing all efforts on his capture.
Pyo has reportedly carjacked a passing vehicle and fleeing
- with a three-year-old hostage.
- Got the mackerel. Should we go?
Police believe Pyo used the cell phone of the vehicle's owner,
and there's evidence he tried to call.
The police told us to come here.
Is the child safe?
Can you at least tell us the parole officers' current location?
We don't have that information.
- You're right here.
- Why won't you say anything?
- Please just confirm it.
- I'm sorry.
(Detective Lee Dong Jin)
Tae Sung, we're not getting anything over here.
That bastard. If he was going to run,
he should've gone alone. Why take a child
I'll get an update from my contact on the police beat,
so Reporter Koo, why don't you head back and start on the research?
What?
Mommy.
Darn it. They're relentless.
You all know the drill, right?
The child's safety is our top priority. So don't get too close,
and don't provoke him.
We wait for the right opportunity to strike.
- Everyone got that?
- Yes.
Shut up, you little brat. Shut your mouth.
Mommy.
Darn it.
(Baby On Board)
That bastard...
Is he out of his mind?
(Senior Bo Na)
Hey, Tae Min.
Go, get that bastard.
Hyun Nam, how's the child?
Thankfully, he doesn't appear to be injured.
I'll get him in the car first.
You're okay.
Mommy.
(Baekmari)
What's wrong? Come on.
Come on, come on. What are you waiting for?
I said, come on.
You bastards. You think I'm some kind of joke?
Go ahead, kill me.
I said, kill me.
Go on, kill me, you bastards.
I'm out of here.
Meeting's over.
(Baekmari)
Actually, Senior Bo Na doesn't like the sight of blood.
She hates watching someone die
in front of her in pain.
That's why she prefers sniping.
She doesn't have to confront them up close,
and she avoids using unnecessarily cruel violence,
or inflicting pain.
It's purely for the objective of making them disappear from this world.
White is up.
But there was an exception for those who hurt children.
That's why the other team members handled those cases until now.
I don't know.
Maybe she thought it was too easy a death for them,
or maybe there was another reason.
Anyway, today,
Senior Bo Na ended up being the one to finish it.
(Not Today)
They're all dead? How?
A car accident, a fall, a drowning.
Another car accident?
Gosh, and even an electrocution.
And what's weird is,
they all died on the day they were released from prison.
Don't you think that's strange?
If they were shot by Kingfisher, that'd be one thing,
but how could every single one of them die
a violent death on the day of their release?
- Call 911, now.
- Okay, okay.
Just bad luck, right? We have to call it a freak accident.
He was such a vicious bastard.
Honestly, even if he had been shot and killed by Kingfisher,
it wouldn't have been strange at all.
(Choi II Hwan (Police Reporter))
Choi, how did it go? On the police side...
We have breaking news. Pyo Gyu Cheol, - What?
- Who cut his ankle monitor and fled...
- Tae Sung, Tae Sung!
After release today, - Look at the news.
Has been found dead after being shot with a sniper rifle.
Mr. Pyo abandoned the stolen vehicle,
and was attempting to escape on a fishing boat docked nearby
when he was shot in the head and fell into the ocean.
He was later found dead.
A blanket too?
All right, got it. Please secure this area.
Thank you.
(Paramedics)
Sir.
The child was safely returned to his parents.
He was found lying on a sofa in the management office.
He was even covered with a blanket.
That's a relief.
Gosh, what is this?
If this was a sniper and not an accident.
I really don't know.
I don't know if we're on the right track or completely barking up the wrong tree.
I feel terrible for Manager Yu.
We should have found a way to handle it ourselves.
Now we've made her a target for the police again.
That's right. There's no way to disguise a sniper attack as an accident.
The bullet is left behind as evidence, like Kingfisher's signature.
Just a little longer. I'm almost done.
Isn't it ironic?
That bullet puts Manager Yu in danger, but instead,
it's protecting all of us.
What is that supposed to mean?
She's basically acting as a decoy.
Diverting the investigation to herself.
Because Manager Yu gets all the attention under the name Kingfisher,
it allows other cases to be quietly buried.
It was the same with the Musan case.
So Manager Yu is in the most dangerous position.
And has the highest risk of being caught.
Bingo.
That's why we all feel so sorry for and grateful to Manager Yu.
But still, besides Manager Yu,
there's no one else who can do this job.
She's the best one we've got.
I'm all done.
Good work.
Here you go.
My, what's all this...
You really don't have to do this for me every time.
You rushed all the way over here from the library
where you were writing your thesis.
- I feel especially bad today.
- To be honest, I was just dozing off.
- Oh, come on.
- Did you get everything taken care of?
I heard a Client filed a complaint last minute.
Thanks to you, yes. It's all sorted out.
- Thank you.
- Mommy.
Yul, sweetie, are you awake?
Yul. Oh, sweetie.
She seemed a little gloomy, and the next thing I knew, she was asleep.
Really? You were?
Yul, I'm so sorry I had to leave when I promised I'd stay with you today.
Then just give me lots of hugs.
Okay, then I'll give you lots and lots of hugs.
You give Mommy a hug too.
How's that, Yul? Feeling a little better now?
Yes, I'm better.
What about you, Mommy?
Me?
I'm okay too.
When I'm holding you like this, everything's all right.
A sniper this time?
Again? On the day of his release?
Tae Sung, what is this?
I think this has something to do with Kingfisher.
Shouldn't we look into this?
The return address on this says it's from Russia.
It's from a friend.
Yul, look. Your mom's friend sent you a doll.
- You're so lucky, Yul.
- It's mine.
- Mommy, give it to me.
- Okay, here you go.
It's mine.
So cute.
So these are Russian letters. What does it say?
It's just a friendly note.
You know, "How are you?" "Miss you," that kind of thing.
That's nice.
You even have friends who send you gifts from overseas.
I guess so. It's nice to have friends.
(You're good at keeping promises. Good. Good night again tonight, Tae Sung)
(A Bona Fide Killer)
Without me knowing, when did our home
- get a new family member?
- A gift came from Russia.
They said they're coming to Korea soon.
He's the troublemaker youngest son of the Royal Family.
Seriously, why did you have to act up?
We need to find out now if it was just an accident,
or a wrongful death disguised as one.
Either way, Chairman Cheon Seong Gyu is at the center of it.
This seems to be a complex and tangled,
and terrifying case.
Kingfisher's M.O. isn't limited to just sniping.
- A joint investigation?
- I'll take care of it.
It's too dangerous for you to be exposed in the field.
Mother.
This is our family's rite, but you make your daughter-in-law do all the work?
I don't think that's fair.
You little brat.
- Goodness.
- Seriously!
Yul... Yul is missing.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)